[{"distractor": ["i, ii, iii, iv, v", "v, iv, iii, i, ii", "ii, iv, iii, v, i"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Arrange in the correct order the following treatment steps for somebody who has lost consciousness(i) \tCall 911 or inform someone of the situation(ii) Begin CPR(iii) Check the patient\u2019s airway to make sure it is clear(iv) Place the victim on his/her back(v) Check signs of life (coughing, breathing, or movement)", "subject": "safety", "support": "Mayo Clinic advises that a first aider should position an unconscious person on his/her back and raise his/her legs by 30 centimeters (12 inches). Raising the patient\u2019s legs above heart level will restore blood flow to the brain. The next step is to loosen the patient\u2019s collar, belt or any other constrictive clothing. In case the person does not regain consciousness, you should call 911 or your local emergency number. Next, check the patient\u2019s airway to ensure it is clear. Finally, the first aid provider should check for signs of life including breathing, coughing or any movement.  If those are absent, begin CPR", "correct_answer": ["iv, i, iii, v, ii"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Move the victim away from the electrical source with a help of a non-conducting object", "Shut off the source of electricity if possible", "Check the victim\u2019s breathing and pulse.  Begin CPR if necessary", "Lay the victim down with his/her head lower than the rest of the body"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Which of the following should you do first when your co-worker has suffered an electrical shock?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Centers of Disease Control and Prevention, CDC specifies the following steps (in this order) to be performed if someone around you has suffered an electrical shock.  <li>Look first. Don\u2019t touch. The person may still be in contact with the electrical source. Touching the person may pass the current through you.</li><li>Call or have someone else call 911 or emergency medical help.<li>Turn off the source of electricity if possible. If not, move the source away from you and the affected person using a non-conducting object made of cardboard, plastic or wood.<li>Once the person is free of the source of electricity, check the persons breathing and pulse. If either has stopped or seems dangerously slow or shallow, begin cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) immediately.<li>If the person is faint or pale or shows other signs of shock, lay the person down with the head slightly lower than the trunk of his or her body and the legs elevated.<li>Don\u2019t touch burns, break blisters, or remove burned clothing. Electrical shock may cause burns inside the body, so be sure the person is taken to a doctor.</li", "correct_answer": ["Call 911 or bring in an emergency medical team"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Call 911 or your local emergency number", "Perform CPR", "Loosen his/her  clothing"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "What first aid should you give to someone who is having a heart attack?", "subject": "safety", "support": "The first thing you should do is call 911 or your local emergency number.  While waiting for health professionals, administer first aid.", "correct_answer": ["All of the above"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Nausea", "Shortness of breath", "Cough"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Which of the following is the most common symptom of a heart attack?", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to Medline Plus at the National Institutes of Health, chest pain is the most common symptom of a heart attack. Chest pain may present in only one part of the patient\u2019s body, or shift from the chest to shoulder, arms, neck, jaw, belly or back", "correct_answer": ["Chest Pain"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Applying ointment over the affected area", "Removing dead skin", "Neutralizing the chemical"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "First aid treatment for a chemical burn involves\u2026", "subject": "safety", "support": "MedlinePlus recommends that you perform the following steps to administer first aid for chemical burns:  You should first remove the cause of the chemical burn. Do not come in contact with the chemical yourself. In case it is a dry chemical, brush off the excess taking care to avoid your eyes. Remove any contaminated jewelry or clothing. Flush the chemicals off the affected area using cool water for 15 minutes or more. If the victim appears faint or pale, or if there is rapid or shallow breathing, treat him/her for shock. Apply cool, wet compresses to relieve the pain. Wrap the affected area with a clean cloth or dry sterile dressing and keep the area away from friction and pressure", "correct_answer": ["Flushing the chemicals off the affected area with cool, gently running water for 10 to 20 minutes"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Yes"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Should you give an over-the-counter medicine to a person who is having a heart attack?", "subject": "safety", "support": "You should not give anything to a heart attack victim unless it is his or her own medication. Ask if the person takes any chest pain medication for a known heart condition, such as nitroglycerin, and help them take it.If the pain does not go away promptly with rest or within 3 minutes of taking nitroglycerin, call for emergency medical help", "correct_answer": ["No"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "When someone swallows a chemical, immediately have the person drink water and then induce vomiting.", "subject": "safety", "support": "While giving water can help dilute a chemical, you should NOT automatically assume that you should induce vomiting in someone who has ingested a chemical. You should call your local Poison Control Center or a doctor and obtain advice on what steps to take", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["First-degree burns", "Second-degree burns"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Which of the following is the most serious burn that destroys skin and underlying tissue?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Third-degree burns are the most serious in nature. In these, all layers of skin are burned and underlying tissues are permanently damaged. Muscles, fat, and even bones may be affected with a third-degree burn. A third-degree burn victim should be treated very cautiously.  Mayo Clinic advises that a first-aider should:  <li>Call 911 or a local emergency number</li><li>Move the victim away from smoke, heat or smoldering materials; not try to remove burned clothing</li><li>Check for victim\u2019s breathing and movement followed by CPR in case the former is absent</li><li>Remove jewelry, belts and other restrictive items, especially from around burned areas and the neck.</li><li><b>NOT</b> immerse burns in cold water as it may lead to hypothermia and weakening of circulation and blood pressure</li><li>Elevate burned body parts above heart level</li><li>Cover the burned area with a cool, moist, sterile bandage or cloth towels.</li", "correct_answer": ["Third-degree burns"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["At 32 F (0\u00b0C)", "Between 120 to 150 F (50 to 70\u00b0C)", "You should never submerge frostbite into water"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "At which water temperature should you bathe frostbitten skin?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Frostbitten body parts should be warmed gradually in water that is 104 to 107.6\u00b0F (40\u00b0 to 42\u00b0C). Additionally, you can wrap or cover the frostbite in a warm blanket. Dont use direct heat, such as a stove, heat lamp, fireplace or heating pad, because these can cause burns before you feel them on your numb skin", "correct_answer": ["Between 104 to 107.6 F (40 to 42\u00b0C)"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Rapid, strong pulse", "Hallucinations", "Throbbing headache", "High body temperature"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Which of these is a symptom of a heatstroke?", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, a person\u2019s body temperature can rise to 106\u00b0F or higher within a span of 10 to 15 minutes, in case of a heatstroke. In the absence of emergency treatment, a person suffering from heatstroke can also die or become physically impaired.  In case you find the above symptoms in your co-worker, CDC advises that you call 911 and inform your supervisor.  Take the patient to a cool, shaded area; spray, sponge, or soak him/her in water; and fan his/her body", "correct_answer": ["All of the above"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Five abdominal thrusts followed by five back blows if needed", "Back blows only", "Abdominal thrusts only"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Which of the following is the correct method for saving someone from choking?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Red Cross recommends a \u201cfive-and-five\u201d approach while delivering first aid to a choking victim.  -Give 5 back blows. First, deliver five back blows between the persons shoulder blades with the heel of your hand. -\tGive 5 abdominal thrusts. Perform five abdominal thrusts (also known as the Heimlich maneuver). -Alternate between 5 blows and 5 thrusts until the blockage is dislodged", "correct_answer": ["Five back blows followed by five abdominal thrusts if necessary"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["ii, iii, iv, i", "i, iii, iv, ii", "iv, ii, iii, i"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Arrange in the correct the steps to take when someone splashes a chemical into the eye.(i) Call a doctor(ii) Take out any contact lenses(iii) Flush the eyes with plenty of water(iv) Wash your hands with soap and water", "subject": "safety", "support": "The first 10 to 15 seconds after exposure to a hazardous substance, especially a corrosive substance, are critical. Delaying treatment, even for a few seconds, may cause serious injury. So, flushing with plenty of water is the first step to take. 20 minutes is generally considered adequate, but for corrosive chemicals as long as 60 minutes may be required", "correct_answer": ["iii, iv, ii, i"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Give rescue breaths only", "Wait for emergency personnel to arrive", "Lift the patient\u2019s head"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "If your co-worker needs CPR but you are not trained in it, which of the following should you do?", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to Mayo Clinic, \u201cIts far better to do something than to do nothing at all if youre fearful that your knowledge or abilities arent 100 percent complete. If youre not trained in CPR, then provide hands-only CPR. That means uninterrupted chest compressions of about 100 a minute until paramedics arrive.  You dont need to try rescue breathing.", "correct_answer": ["Perform chest compressions only"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "You are not required to ask a victim\u2019s permission to perform first aid.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Practitioners of first aid need to obtain advance consent or permission, the so-called \u201cexpressed consent\u201d from the patient. To obtain consent, you should identify yourself, describe your level of medical training, and ask if it is all right to help. While administering first aid to an unresponsive victim, consent is implied or assumed, given that a reasonable person would grant permission to receive first aid care if able to do so", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Airway, breastbone, chest", "Airway, breathing, circulation", "Back, circulation, airway"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "What is the correct order of airway, breathing, and circulation in the CPR process?", "subject": "safety", "support": "In 2010, the American Heart Association (AHA) changed CPR\u2019s longstanding A-B-C (Airway, Breathing, Compressions) sequence to C-A-B (Compressions, Airway, Breathing.", "correct_answer": ["Chest compressions, airway, breathing"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Apply pressure on the wound with a clean cloth or bandage", "Apply an antibiotic to the wound", "Cover the wound"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-first-aid-quiz", "question": "Which of the following should you NOT do while treating cuts and scrapes?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Although cuts and scrapes do not require the victim to visit an emergency room, proper care is needed to avoid infections. If you\u2019re treating wounds, Mayo Clinic advises you to stop the bleeding by applying gentle pressure on the wound for 20 to 30 minutes; use clear water to clean the wound and tweezers cleaned with alcohol to remove particles from the wound, if there are any; avoid using soap as it may cause irritation; apply an antibiotic to the affected area; cover the wound to keep harmful bacteria out; and change the dressing regularly or when it becomes wet or dirty. For wounds that are deeper than \u00bc inch or 6 millimeters, visit a health practitioner to get stitches", "correct_answer": ["Wash the wound with soap"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Most food allergies are caused by contact with the proteins in milk, eggs, fish, Crustacean shellfish, tree nuts, wheat, peanuts, or soybeans. Persons experience allergic reactions only by consuming these foods.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Persons can have an allergic reaction by cross-contact with the proteins in one of these foods during food preparation. Cross-contact is when the protein of an allergy-causing food comes in contact with another food. Cross-contact can happen when using the same cooking oil, utensils, cutting boards, food containers, gloves, fryers, and grills for both items of food", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Fish and Shellfish \u2013 145 degrees Fahrenheit", "Leftovers - 165 degrees Fahrenheit", "Ground beef \u2013 160 degrees Fahrenheit"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "The following is a list of food items and the minimum internal food temperature at which they should be cooked. Which of these is incorrect?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Eggs should be cooked at a minimum internal temperature of 160 degree Fahrenheit. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention explains why: \u201cA type of bacterium, Salmonella, can be on both the outside and inside of eggs that appear to be normal, and if the eggs are eaten raw or lightly cooked, the bacterium can cause illness.", "correct_answer": ["Eggs \u2013 145 degrees Fahrenheit"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Physical, biological, and radiological", "Physical, psychological, and health", "Physical, chemical, and psychosocial"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Which three major factors cause food contamination?", "subject": "safety", "support": "People can get sick by consuming food contaminated by the following three major hazards:  Physical- objects such ashair, nails, jewelry, glass, staples, and bandages in food are categorized as physical hazards. Chemical- substances that are added during food handling or that occur naturally can cause food-borne illness. Examples include certain metals, pesticides, and cleaning agents. Biological- germs that are not visible to the naked eye like those carried by bacteria, viruses, and parasites", "correct_answer": ["Physical, biological, and chemical"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["In the microwave", "On the counter", "In a sink of hot water"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "How should you thaw perishable food?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Perishable foods should be thawed under cold running water or in the refrigerator. When thawed in the microwave, food should be cooked promptly afterwards. According to the USDA, \u201cPerishable foods should never be thawed on the counter or in hot water and must not be left at room temperature for more than two hours.", "correct_answer": ["Under cold running water"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["1.5 hours", "3 hours", "3.5 hours"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "What is the maximum amount of time perishable food should be left out?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Perishable food should not be left out more than 2 hours at room temperature (1 hour when the temperature is above 90 \u00b0F)", "correct_answer": ["2 hours"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Individuals who are lactose-intolerant can consume pasteurized milk without negative side effects.", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to U.S Food and Drug Administration, \u201cPasteurizing milk DOES NOT cause lactose intolerance and allergic reactions. But, both raw milk and pasteurized milk can cause allergic reactions in people sensitive to milk proteins.", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "You can always smell, see, or taste harmful bacteria in food that can cause illness.", "subject": "safety", "support": "United States Department of Agriculture (USDA) states that you cannot always see, taste, or smell harmful bacteria that may cause illness", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["One and a half", "Two and a half", "Three"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Perishable foods should be refrigerated within ___ hours of purchase.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Foodsafety.gov advises that perishable foods should be stored within 2 hours after purchasing. In case the climate temperature is equal to or higher than 90\u00b0F (as during summers), the time should be cut down to 1 hour.Additionally, the site notes,\u201cMake sure your fridge and freezer are cooled to the right temperature. Your fridge should be between 40\u00b0F and 32\u00b0F, and your freezer should be 0\u00b0F or below.", "correct_answer": ["Two"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["10 to 30 days", "2 to 6 months", "2 to 4 years"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "How long can high-acid canned food such as tomatoes be stored?", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to the United States Department of Agriculture (USDA), \u201cIn general, high-acid canned food such as tomatoes, grapefruit, and pineapple can be stored on the shelf for 12 to 18 months. Low-acid canned food such as meat, poultry, fish, and most vegetables will keep 2 to 5 years \u2014 if the can remains in good condition and has been stored in a cool, clean, and dry place.", "correct_answer": ["12 to 18 months"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Raw meat", "Raw vegetables", "Unpasteurized dairy products"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following foods is most commonly associated with Salmonella?", "subject": "safety", "support": "As per healthvermont.gov, \u201cSalmonella is commonly found in raw food products that come from animals, such as eggs, egg products, meat, meat products, unpasteurized milk, or other unpasteurized dairy products. Thorough cooking and processing effectively kills salmonella bacteria.", "correct_answer": ["Just a and c"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["CDC", "FDA", "EPA"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following agencies inspects, grades, and enforces standards of quality and wholesomeness for meat, poultry, milk, eggs, and grains?", "subject": "safety", "support": "The United States Department of Agriculture (informally called the USDA or Agriculture Department) is the federal executive division formed to develop and execute U.S. federal government policy on food, farming and agriculture", "correct_answer": ["USDA"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "There is nothing wrong with using the same knife for cutting vegetables that you use for raw meats, poultry, seafood, and eggs.", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to the Kansas State University Research and Extension Service, one of the most common food safety errors people make is \u201ccross contamination.\u201d Cross-contamination takes place when disease-causing organisms are transferred from one type of food to another. One such example is using the same knife to first cut or slice raw meat and then vegetables.  Following a good food safety practice requires you to wash hands before and after touching cooked or raw foods; clean cutting boards before cutting anything; clean utensils; and place cooked meats and raw meats separately on different plates. All of this can drastically reduce food-borne illness", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Infants", "Pregnant women", "People with weakened immune systems (those with HIV/AIDS, cancer, diabetes etc)"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-food-safety-quiz", "question": "Everyone is at a risk of contracting a food-borne illness. However, some are at a greater risk of falling ill or even dying of infection, including:", "subject": "safety", "support": "United States Department of Agriculture says, \u201cEveryone is at risk for getting a foodborne illness. However, some people are at greater risk for experiencing a more serious illness or even death should they get a food borne illness. Those at greater risk are infants, young children, pregnant women and their unborn babies, older adults, and people with weakened immune systems (such as those with HIV/AIDS, cancer, diabetes, kidney disease, and transplant patients.)", "correct_answer": ["All of the above"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Use a fire extinguisher to put out the fire, even if you\u2019ve never used a fire extinguisher before", "Stay in the building until you figure out a way to extinguish the fire", "Run out of the building without warning others of the fire"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "When you discover a fire, you should\u2026", "subject": "safety", "support": "When you discover a fire, you should do the following: help the people in immediate danger; alert everyone around you by shouting \u201cFire!\u201d; pull the fire alarm; call the fire department;, and close the door behind you to help confine the fire. Just be sure not to lock the door, so that the fire department can get in. Finally, of course, leave the building with your co-workers", "correct_answer": ["Pull the fire alarm and call the fire department"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "All workplaces need to provide portable fire extinguishers.", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to OSHA, employers are not required to provide portable fire extinguishers in the office. But if they do, they must set up an educational program to acquaint employees with the general principles of fire extinguisher use", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["False"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Even when there are no signs of a fire, you should respond to every fire alarm as if it were real.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Every fire alarm should receive the same reaction, regardless of whether there is actually a fire or not.  Even when you do not see any signs of fire, you should take appropriate steps when an alarm is sounded. Moreover, all false alarms should be reported to the authorities", "correct_answer": ["True"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Class A water fire extinguishers", "Class C dry chemical fire extinguisher", "None of the above"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following fire extinguishers is used to put out fires caused by flammable liquids?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Flammable liquids include oils, gasoline, paints, grease, lacquers, and solvents", "correct_answer": ["Class B carbon dioxide fire extinguisher"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["CO2", "Water", "Multi-purpose dry chemical", "Both a and b"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following fire extinguishers is used to put out Class A fires?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Class A fires include fires in ordinary combustibles: paper, wood, cloth, rubber, and many plastics. Water based fire extinguishers and multi-purpose dry chemical based fire extinguishers are suitable for Class A fires. However, ordinary dry chemical fire extinguishers are suitable for only Class B and Class C fires", "correct_answer": ["Both b and c"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Open the doors and windows to let the smoke out", "Break windows", "Breathe through your mouth"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following should you do if you are unable to evacuate a burning building?", "subject": "safety", "support": "If you\u2019re unable to escape the building, you should create an area of refuge by-  - Sealing the room. Stuff wet cloth around cracks in doors, and seal up vents. This stops the smoke from coming through such openings. - Keeping windows and doors closed. Do not break windows. Smoke and flames can come in from the inside. Crack open a window slightly if you need air. - Staying low under smoke. Smoke, heat, and poisonous gases rise, leaving the freshest air closer to the floor. Remember to cover your nose and mouth with a wet cloth. - Breathing only through your nose. - Hanging something in the window to signal for help", "correct_answer": ["Stay low under the smoke"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Fire doors should be locked at all times.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Fire doors are often blocked open for the convenience of visitors and employees. However, this can create a break in the fire barrier leading to a fire hazard. According to OSHA, fire doors must not be held open or tied open by devices such as blocks, door wedges etc.  They must also never be locked or blocked when employees are inside. Fire doors can only be held open by a device that automatically releases when the fire alarm is activated", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["5", "20", "25"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Workplaces with a minimum of ____ employees need to have a written fire prevention program in place.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Employers should provide their workers with the fire prevention plan in writing when there are 11 or more employees at a workplace. In a workplace with 10 or fewer employees, the fire prevention plan may be communicated verbally", "correct_answer": ["11"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["At the top of the fire", "At the center of the fire", "Away from the fire"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Where should you aim a fire extinguisher nozzle when putting out a fire?", "subject": "safety", "support": "You should always aim at the base of the fire and never the flames. To put out a fire, it is important that you extinguish the fuel. If you aim at the flames, the extinguishing agent will fly through them without putting out the fire", "correct_answer": ["At the base of the fire"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "During a fire, when a stairwell is unavailable because it is disabled or inaccessible, it is okay to use the elevators when exiting a building.", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to the National Fire Protection Agency, using the elevator in the event of a fire or any other building emergency is never appropriate, even in a two-story building. The elevator may malfunction or travel to a fire floor, exposing occupants to the fire.  There is also an increased risk of smoke inhalation, because smoke may enter the elevator through shafts and travel towards the roof of the building. If caught in this scenario, wait for the fire rescue to arrive for assistance.", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Class A - Cloth, wood, paper, and rubber", "Class C - Wiring, fuse boxes, electrical equipment, and computers", "Class D - Combustible metals such as magnesium, potassium, titanium, and sodium", "Class K - Cooking fluids such as fats and oils"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Below is a list of fire extinguisher types matched with surfaces on which they can be used. Which is the incorrect option?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Class B fire extinguishers use carbon dioxide as the fire-fighting agent and can extinguish oils, paints, lacquers, grease, solvents, and flammable liquids. Fires on plastic surfaces can be put out via a Class A fire extinguisher, which uses water", "correct_answer": ["Class B - Plastics, polyethylene, styrofoam"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Within two days of the initial assignment", "Within 30 days of the initial assignment", "Within 90 days of the initial assignment"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "When should employees be informed of the fire hazards to which they are exposed at work?", "subject": "safety", "support": "OSHA Standard number 1910.39(d) states, \u201cAn employer must inform employees upon initial assignment to a job of the fire hazards to which they are exposed. An employer must also review with each employee those parts of the fire prevention plan necessary for self-protection.", "correct_answer": ["Upon the initial assignment"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["False"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "A portable fire extinguisher should only be used by trained employees.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Employers can choose to authorize some or all employees to use portable extinguishers. In both cases, employers should provide employees sufficient training to do so", "correct_answer": ["True"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["True"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "The primary function of a fire door is to exit a building in case of fire.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Although in some cases fire doors are used as emergency exits in the event of a fire, the primary function of a fire door is to act as a fire barrier and contain fire and smoke to prevent it from entering parts of the building unaffected by fire at the time", "correct_answer": ["False"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Evacuate a building through designated exit routes", "Keep fire doors shut to prevent the fire from spreading", "Crawl low under the smoke while breathing only through your nose"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following should you NOT do during a fire emergency?", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to the U.S Fire Administration, you should not go back inside a burning building. Apart from the risk of burning, the increasingly depleted oxygen levels and high amount of toxic gases could pose a great hazard to your life. Leave the fire-fighting to the authorities, even if you know that someone is stuck inside the burning building.", "correct_answer": ["Re-enter the building without the permission of authorities"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["PULL", "PUSH", "None of the above"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-fire-safety-quiz", "question": "Which of the following is the acronym describing the correct sequence of using a fire extinguisher?", "subject": "safety", "support": "The extinguisher should be discharges using the P.A.S.S technique \u2013 pull, aim, squeeze, and sweep.  - <b>P</b>ull the pin to break the tamper seal. - <b>A</b>im low, pointing the nozzle of the fire extinguisher at the base of the fire. - <b>S</b>queeze the handle to release the extinguishing agent. - <b>S</b>weep from one side to the other at the base of the fire till it extinguishes. - Repeat in the event of re-ignition", "correct_answer": ["PASS"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Decreased productivity", "Psychological and physical stress", "Interrupted concentration and communication", "Accidents and injuries at work due to one's inability to hear warning signals"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-hearing-conservation-quiz", "question": "Which of the following is a long-term negative result of loud noise exposure?", "subject": "safety", "support": "According to OSHA, exposure to loud noise can result in a drop in productivity, get in the way of clear and smooth communication, interfere in concentration, and lead to workplace accidents and injuries when warning signals are hard to hear.", "correct_answer": ["All of the above"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["System Level Monitor", "Sound Loudness Methods", "Service Lifecycle Management"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-hearing-conservation-quiz", "question": "To what does the acronym SLM refer?", "subject": "safety", "support": "The Sound Level Meter is an instrument used to measure noise levels", "correct_answer": ["Sound Level Meter"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["Ear Muffs", "Pre-molded plugs", "Foam plugs", "Canal caps"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-hearing-conservation-quiz", "question": "Which of the following is NOT a type of hearing protection?", "subject": "safety", "support": "Ear muffs block noise by covering the outer ear completely. In contrast, pre-molded plugs \u2013 which come in a variety of sizes and are constructed using silicone, rubber or plastic \u2013 plugs seal the ear canal. While fitting these plugs, one should not experience discomfort. Canal caps often resemble earplugs on a flexible plastic or metal band", "correct_answer": ["Cotton balls"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["9", "10", "11"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-hearing-conservation-quiz", "question": "Baseline audiograms should be provided with ____ months of an employee\u2019s first exposure to a noise level equal to or exceeding an average of 85 decibels every hour for eight hours.", "subject": "safety", "support": "The baseline audiogram is the initial audiogram against which all future ones are compared, to yield a measure of hearing change.  Employers are required by OSHA to present baseline audiograms within six months of a worker\u2019sfirst exposure to noise level equal to or exceeding an 8-hour TWA (Time Weighted Average) of 85 decibels. OSHA allows an exception only when employer makes use of a mobile test van for an audiogram, which allows for another six months of leeway, up to a year within the initial exposure to overly loud noise.  ", "correct_answer": ["6"], "difficulty": 0}, {"distractor": ["False"], "url": "https://www.mysafetysign.com/free-hearing-conservation-quiz", "question": "Noise-induced hearing loss can be temporary.", "subject": "safety", "support": "Temporary hearing loss results from short-term exposures to noise, with normal hearing returning after period of rest. Generally, prolonged exposure to high noise levels over a period of time gradually causes permanent damage", "correct_answer": ["True"], "difficulty": 0}]